—⊸ JON FOSTER ⊶

SOLUTIONS-ORIENTED, CUSTOMER-CENTRIC SALES LEADER

CONTACT



210.630.1120



∠ 4jonathanfoster@gmail

PROFILE

B2B & B2C solutions-oriented, customer-centric activator with 10+ years sales experience specializing in technical sales and services -- obsessed with putting the customer first – solve problems by approaching with a mutually beneficial solutions mindset for both customers and businesses alike. Long-term customer relationship management, in-person and in-system, with a drive for metrics and personalization research are key to success in this industry and beyond. Let's go!

SKILLS

- PROBLEM SOLVING
- **RESOURCEFUL**
- **SELF-STARTER**
- **TEAM-FIRST MENTALITY**
- **SOLUTIONS ORIENTED**
- **CRM & PERSONALIZATION**
- SDR / BDR / MDR / OSR

EDUCATION

AS, BUSINESS

2010-2012

Northwest Vista College

SOLUTIONS SALES TRAINING

2015-Present

Cavender Toyota

B2B WATER SUSTAINABILITY

2013-2015

Sustainable Water Services

EXPERIENCE

Service Advisor

Cavender Toyota, San Antonio TX

2019-2020

Responsible for cross-sell/upsell services to current customers with 100% quota attainment + consistent bonus target achievement. Applied a technical background to understanding mechanical and maintenance knowledge to an educational approach with the customers to personalize their experience based on vehicle. Held Top 5 in Survey volume and score for entire tenure; trained and onboarded 3 new hires.

Sales Consultant

Cavender Toyota, San Antonio TX

2015-2019

Responsible for end-to-end sales process from front door to Finance, self-managed quota attainment for majority of tenure; consistently sought to train other SAs in technical product knowledge and consultation techniques. Trained in objection handling, solutions-oriented approach and business development rep (BDR) tactics; trained and onboarded new hires throughout. Hit the number then hit the pavement!

Sales Associate

Sears Hometown Showroom

2014-2015

Responsible for customer engagement and end-to-end sales process for Sears Homeroom appliances; held number one spot in Home Warranty sales throughout. Additional duties included opening and closing, cashier, accounting, and scoping bestin-class packages for customers based on best-fit products for their use-case.

B2B Solutions Consultant

2013-2015

Sold half a million dollar recycled water solutions to enterprises in the Central region.